# Céline Blandin

Ethical Hacker - Pentester

As a **penetration tester**, I specialize in identifying system vulnerabilities, adapting methodologies to client systems, and adhering to **OWASP** standards. With extensive **Project Management** experience, I excel in problem-solving, planning, and organizing, while effectively managing teams, clients, subcontractors, and project deadlines and budgets.

# Experience

#### Al Trainer

August 2024 - Today - OUTLIER

Teaching Artificial Intelligence to understand user inputs and make decisions.

#### Pentester

April 2023 - November 2023 - YINKOZI, Ltd

Manual pentests on governmental web applications and API. On-site with client 4 days per week.

*Workshop for developers,* vulnerabilities explanation, and discussion.

Presentation for one of the largest international Bank: "Low Code/No Code application and Security"

# Pentester - Bug Bounty

February 2023 - Today - HACKERONE

Web Application Security Testing: pentest, client Report, Follow up with client

## CTF - Level 10 / Top 5%

September 2022 - Today - TryHackMe

#### Offensive Pentesting - Jr Penetration Tester

Completion of CTF rooms: Vulnerability Scanning, Password Cracking, Metasploit, Buffer Overflow Exploitation, Active Directory, Burp Suite, Nmap, OWASP, Nessus, Metasploit

#### Speaker

November 2021 - Today - FREELANCE

Lycée Theodore Monod – UAE

#### Cybersecurity and its impacts

Presentation to French students in Grade 12

What is cybersecurity, how it works, real-world impacts and consequences (cyberwarfare, geopolitics effects), tips

#### Introduction to Cybersecurity

Presentation to French students in Grades 3 to 12

Alliance Française - UAE

#### Introduction to Cybersecurity – Best practices

Presentation to the French community via Français du Monde ADFE

Lycée Louis Massignon and Lycée Theodore Monod – UAE **Cyberbullying** 

Presentation to French school staff, parents and students

# Personal Info

Phone

+1 346 281 9679

E-mail

linceblandin@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/celine-blandin

Portfolio

https://github.com/linceBLA/linceBLA

# **Programming Languages**

Linux

Pre-advanced

C ••••

Pre-advanced

Python

Intermediate

HTLM5 - CSS3

Intermediate

# Languages

French

Native

English ••••

Business fluent

Spanish ••••

Business fluent

## **Community Manager**

September 2016 - May 2017 - FREELANCE

French and Argentinian Self-contractors, ARGENTINA

Websites and Facebook pages creation and follow up, online stores set up on contractor's websites and commercials such as "Mercado Libre", Web Marketing analysis and coaching

#### Technical Translator, Writer

*November 2013 - March 2014* Les Navigauteurs, ARGENTINA

## **Project Manager**

May 2011 - December 2012 - VDM Construction, AUSTRALIA

Management of the Maintenance service in WA: 14 active projects closed, within budget with client's satisfaction. Preparation of Mining projects according to tender frames and budgets.

#### **Estimator**

March 2010 - May 2011 - ONESTEEL Reinforcing, AUSTRALIA and NEW ZEALAND Estimating project, following projects.

## **Project Manager**

January 2006 - January 2009 - BOUYGUES CONSTRUCTION, Paris, FRANCE

Project Management of 5 building sites, on time, and budget, without HSE events, and with client satisfaction. Responsible for around 70 people on site.

# **Business Developer**

January 2005 - December 2005 - GA Enterprise, Toulouse, FRANCE

Establishing technical and general specifications for contracts according to the client's satisfaction.

# **Education and Training**

# Master's Degree - Civil Engineering

2002/2005

Institut National des Sciences Appliquées (INSA), Toulouse

#### CEHv12 - EC-COUNCIL

September 2024

Scored 121/125 - 96.8%

# CompTIA Security+

June-July 2022

The exam was taken in person at MontRoyal Elevate center in Abu Dhabi

#### **Python**

February 2022

Udemy

#### Ethical Hacking

November 2019 - December 2020

Udemy

# Linux & C Programming language

2019

Openclassrooms

# Wireless Ethical Hacking & Penetration Testing

September 2019

Edusphere, Hands-on Masterclass, Dubai